# **Denis Arce**

San Antonio, Texas Metropolitan Area



dnsarce21@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/denis-arce-81163a6b

### **Summary**

Experienced Operations Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the dental health, leisure, travel & tourism industry. Skilled in Relationship building, Negotiation, Budgeting, Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, and Microsoft Word. Strong professional graduated from Heritage University.

## **Experience**



### **Full Stack Developer**

#### Freelance

Sep 2021 - Present (1 month +)

Full Stack Developer with 6 months of experience designing, developing and implementing applications and solutions using a range of technologies and programing languages. Seeking to gain broad development experience and hands-on technical expertise in a challenging role as a Full Stack Developer.

### ✓ CSR II

Bank of America

Jun 2019 - Sep 2021 (2 years 4 months)

# **Operations Manager**

Pacific Dental Services
Sep 2017 - Jun 2019 (1 year 10 months)

# Assistant Manager

Enterprise Holdings
Mar 2015 - Aug 2017 (2 years 6 months)

### **Education**



#### The University of Texas at San Antonio

Software Engineer, Computer Software Engineering
Jun 2021 - Jan 2022

# Heritage University

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management, General 2010 - 2014

### **Skills**

Customer Service • PowerPoint • Microsoft Word • Microsoft Office • Microsoft Excel • Research • Teamwork • Social Media • Outlook • Strategic Planning